Guide to the George Charles Poppensiek papers, 1942-2013.
Poppensiek, George Charles papers
- Series VII. Other Writings and Publications
  - Cornell University Announcements, N. Y. S. Veterinary College, 1971-1974 (Box 17)
  - Cornell University Announcements, N. Y. S. Veterinary College, 1959-1971 (Box 17)
  - N. Y. S. College of Veterinary Medicine, Alumni Directory, Centennial Edition, 1994 (Box 17)
  - Anabolics in Animal Production: Public Health Aspects, analytical methods and regulation (Symposium held at OIE), February 1983 (Box 17)
  - Report of the Regional Educational Programme for Animal Health Assistants (REPAHO)/UNDP/PAHO/WHO Evaluation Mission, May 1982 (Box 17)
  - Research Program Evaluation, College of Veterinary Medicine, Mississippi State University, 1981 (Box 17)
  - Foreign Animal Diseases (Course Book), 1988 (Box 17)
  - A Study of the Need for Equine Diagnostic Services and a Proposal for Implementation, State of New Jersey, 1977 (Box 17)
  - Argentine - United States Joint Commission on Foot-and-Mouth Disease, Final Report, 1974 (Box 17)
  - George C. Poppensiek: Publications, 1946-1973 (Box 17)
  - Establishment of a College of Veterinary Medicine at the University of Arizona: Feasibility Study, 1977 (Box 17)
  - Animal Diseases, Parasites and Human Health, 1985 (Box 17)
  - Evaluation: Teaching of Infectious Diseases, College of Veterinary Medicine, University of Florida, 1981 (Box 17)
  - The Impact of University Reform on Veterinary Medical Education, Poppensiek and Craig, 1970 (Box 17)
  - Report of the Doctor of Veterinary Medicine Degree Program, for the Boardof Regents, State of Louisiana, 1980 (Box 17)
  - Glimpses of the Future for Post-Graduate Education in Veterinary Medicine, 1971 (Box 17)
  - A Study of the Need for Equine Diagnostic Services and a Proposal for Implementation, State of New Jersey, 1977 (Box 17)